JUAN CRUZ MARQUEZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

353 4124 866

marquezjuanchy@hotmail.com

www.juancruzmarquez.com.ar

Villa Maria, Cordoba, Argentina

SKILLS

Python React Docker

PostgreSQL Nestjs HTML

CSS Typescript Mariadb

Javascript Linux SCRUM

EDUCATION

UTN

2019-2024 Systems Engineer

UNSAM

2020

Python Course

Udemv

Master in javascript

Node

Instituto La Santísima Trinidad

2008-2014

Secondary School - Bachelor's degree in economics and administration

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - C1 - Advanced

ABOUT ME

I am a predisposed, honest, sincere and cordial person. Learning to program since 2019. With knowledge in logic and programming languages. Great capacity for analysis and adaptation to new projects with agile learning. With experience in Full Stack development of web services.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

VEMO 2023-Present

I am currently in charge of the backend of the OMS (Operational Management System) module of VEMO. This module is responsible for the management, administration and control of schedules, shifts, and driver schedules. I also develop the Auth project, management and administration of users, permissions and roles. I use technologies like Typescript, NestJS, Postgres, Azure Bus, Docker, etc.

Full Stack Developer

KPMG 2022-2023

Development of Backend services with Typescript, NestJS, and database management technology. Frontend services development with technology such as React, TailwindCSS, Typescript. Development of scripts to automate the reading of PDF files with Python and databases.

Tutor Teacher

UTN 2023

Tutor teacher in Testing Argentina 4.0 Program - UTN. Help to students who took the course, correction of practices and group assembly.

Full Stack Developer

Casa Vila 2019-2022

I was responsible for creating an inventory management system. I used technologies such as Python, React and Postgres to develop an application that would allow real-time tracking of available products, manage sales and generate inventory reports.